<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project</string>
    <string name="side_plank">
        <strong>Exercise: Side Plank</strong> \n
        <strong>Steps:</strong> \n
        1. Begin by lying on your side with your legs straight.\n
        2. Prop yourself up using your forearm, ensuring your elbow is directly below your shoulder.\n
        3. Engage your core muscles and raise your body, keeping your body in a straight line from head to heels.\n
        4. Hold this position for the desired duration, maintaining a straight spine and avoiding sagging or arching.\n
        5. Gently lower yourself back down and switch to the other side to balance the workout.\n
        <strong>Benefits:</strong> \n
        1. Strengthens three muscle groups at once \n
        2. Protects your spine \n
        3. Strengthens your core without stressing your back \n
    </string>

    <string name="lunges">
        <strong>Exercise: Lunges</strong> \n
        <strong>Steps:</strong> \n
        1. Start by standing straight with your feet hip-width apart.\n
        2. Take a step forward with one leg, lowering your hips until both knees are bent at about a 90-degree angle.\n
        3. Ensure your front knee is directly above your ankle and not pushed too far forward.\n
        4. Your back knee should be just above the floor, but not touching it.\n
        5. Push back up to the starting position using your front heel.\n
        6. Alternate legs and repeat the movement for the desired number of repetitions.\n
        <strong>Benefits:</strong> \n
        1. Lunges target hips, glutes, quads, hamstrings, and calves. \n
        2. Improves balance and flexibility. \n
        3. Enhances range of motion. \n
    </string>

    <string name="push_ups">
        <strong>Exercise: Push-Ups</strong> \n

        <strong>Benefits:</strong> \n
        1.  Targets chest, shoulders, and arms. \n
        2.  Engages core muscles for stability. \n
        3.  Boosts overall endurance and strength. \n
    </string>

    <string name="abs_crunches">
        <strong>Exercise: Abdominal Crunches</strong> \n

        <strong>Benefits:</strong> \n
        1.  Focuses on core and abdominal muscles. \n
        2.  Strengthens the core for stability and support. \n
        3.  Aids in improving flexibility of the spine. \n
    </string>

    <string name="stepping">
        <strong>Exercise: High Stepping</strong> \n
        <strong>Benefits:</strong> \n
        1.  Increases heart rate, aiding in cardio fitness. \n
        2.  Engages and strengthens leg muscles. \n
        3.  Reduces stress on joints while exercising. \n
    </string>
</resources>
